{
    "id": "2599e023655d4bc7bc318b4e2a851aae",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "February is the …………………….. month of the year.",
            "description": "We use a superlative adjective after the.",
            "answers": [
                "short",
                "shorter",
                "shortest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "be8924d12cc34ae0b513399759609413"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mary is …………………….. than Susan.",
            "description": "We use a comparative adjective before than.",
            "answers": [
                "pretty",
                "prettier",
                "prettiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c69b0a622a344794be7d24c3f4dec22d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cycling is ……………………… than driving.",
            "description": "We use a comparative adjective before than.",
            "answers": [
                "healthy",
                "healthier",
                "healthiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "914c387e0455452990e4b0a547738f3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is your grandmother any …………………….. today?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fdf849defe7f4fcf9f29c7d292215006"
        },
        {
            "question": "A refrigerator is ………………………. than a television.",
            "description": "Use a comparative expression before than.",
            "answers": [
                "useful",
                "more useful",
                "most useful"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1de48045de3f49a8ba9414aee6e1d446"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is as ……………………. as a stick.",
            "description": "We use a positive adjective when we make comparisons with as…as.",
            "answers": [
                "thin",
                "thinner",
                "thinnest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fdad0ad64ebb4d7caadde0eb1f9dd18a"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the ………………………. movie I have ever seen.",
            "description": "Best is the superlative form of good.",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "gooder",
                "goodest",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "af0338de488d447a8033db5aa8949c1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am the ………………………… mother in the world.",
            "description": "We use a superlative adjective after the.",
            "answers": [
                "lucky",
                "luckier",
                "luckiest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a8d29713e33b47d986fbd8a47a7bc7cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ………………………. than that.",
            "description": "Worse is the comparative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "bad",
                "badder",
                "worse"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f830117547354b9dbbfa6f771375fa9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the ………………………. update from the border?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "last",
                "later",
                "latest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ec10c2d768d34828af701e937a347f50"
        },
        {
            "question": "Honey is ………………………. than milk.",
            "description": "Sweeter is the comparative form of sweet.",
            "answers": [
                "sweet",
                "sweeter",
                "sweetest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb7b978c9208425b90cc77c6fadd6fb0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She earns a lot ……………………. money than I do.",
            "description": "More is the comparative form of much.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db5ca593f1e2471baa824a8ff8f3b35f"
        }
    ]
}